人人影視傾情奉獻
翻譯  草草
時間軸  Kallen
顧問  老杜
后期  餓得慌
校對  草草
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第四季  第七集
...支持我改革民主黨的努力
...supporting my efforts to reform the Democratic Party...
恢復總統辦公室的正直
and to restore integrity to the Oval Office.
很遺憾
Unfortunately,
我將無法完成我期望達成的目標
I won't be able to complete the work I set out to achieve.
顯然  我的競選已經成了
It has become clear that my candidacy has become
鬧劇而非出路
a distraction rather than a solution...
爭議已經蓋過了問題
that controversy has trumped the issues.
因此  我將結束
And for that reason, I am ending my bid...
對民主黨總統候選人的競選
...to be the Democratic nominee for president.
鄧巴退出競選
安德伍德成為僅剩的民主黨候選人
以上是希瑟·鄧巴在華盛頓的競選總部發表的講話
That was Heather Dunbar from her campaign headquarters in Washington.
鄧巴退出后  安德伍德總統
With Dunbar out, that leaves President Underwood
將成為預計提名人
as the presumptive nominee.
現在的焦點  是安德伍德總統將與誰...
The focus now is on who President Underwood's running--
早上好
Good morning.
媽媽
Mommy?
你好  親愛的
Hello, darling.
-我想吃早餐  -你想吃早餐
- I want breakfast. - You want breakfast?
-爸爸呢  -他在準備上班
- Where's Daddy? - Oh, he's getting ready for work.
我要給你剪頭
I'm gonna cut your hair.
-不不不  -我要給你剪頭
- No! No! No! - I'm gonna cut your hair.
-不不不  -為什么說"不"啊
- No! No! No! No! - What do you mean "No"?
不
No!
我要把你剪成小禿子
I'm gonna make you a little bald boy.
不  剃媽媽的頭  別剃我的
No! No, shave Mom's head, not mine!
剃媽媽的頭  好吧
Shave Mom's head? Okay.
-不  不  -我來剃媽媽的頭
- No! No! - I'll shave Mom's head.
-不  -我來剃媽媽的頭
- No. - I'll shave Mom's head.
我們最近太急了
We've been moving so quickly.
或許該退后一步  好好考慮一下
Maybe we should take a step back. Think this through again.
我們不能跟彼此別扭  克萊爾
We can't afford to be weird with each other, Claire.
別扭  什么意思
Weird? What do you mean?
我在廁所里看到你了  那么看著我
I saw you in the bathroom... looking at me.
不是第一次了
It's not the first time.
有時候我想說些話  卻不知該說什么
Sometimes I want to say something, I just don't know what to say.
-這很不舒服  -或許會永遠如此
- It's uncomfortable. - Maybe it will always be like that.
但我們得排除那些  不能讓它影響我們的計劃
But we have to separate that out. It can't affect our plan.
因為這是唯一
Because that's the one thing...
我們已經想明白了的
that we have figured out.
沃克和瓦斯奎茲
When Walker and Vasquez...
背叛我們
betrayed us,
把說好給我的國務卿給了別人時
pulled the Secretary of State right out from under my feet,
當時不容我們有疑慮  是你提醒了我
there was no room for doubt, and you made me remember that.
我們走上了一條路
We took a path...
一條艱難的路
a difficult one,
因為完全無法保證這條路會通往何方
because we had no guarantee where it was going to lead us.
那需要莫大的勇氣
It took a steel goddamn stomach,
自此之后我們不得不做的一切都是如此
and so has everything else we had to do since.
所以現在別去擔心你和我
So don't worry about you and me now.
找到你的勇氣  克萊爾
Find your steel, Claire.
感謝大家前來
Thank you all very much for coming.
你看到這個了嗎
Have you seen this?
哈里發國  哈里發帝國組織
ICO. Islamic Caliphate Organization.
哈里發國占領了庫爾德要塞
領袖是艾哈邁德和尤瑟夫·艾哈邁迪
Ahmed and Yusuf Al Ahmadi.
他們一直精明地分開行動
They've been smart about keeping split up.
萬一一個死了  另一個就接管
If one dies, the other takes over.
但他們要在北敘利亞召開策劃會議
But they're holding a planning session in northern Syria.
現在兩人都在那里
Both are there right now.
約旦河谷的事我被整得很慘
I got my ass handed to me over the Jordan Valley.
我不能批準發動導彈襲擊
I'm not gonna launch a missile strike
除非我相信國家安全受到嚴重威脅
unless I believe that there's an overwhelming national security threat,
而我不認為他們構成這種威脅
and I'm just not convinced that they pose one.
總統認為哈里發國是嚴重威脅
The president believes ICO to be a serious threat.
我們認為他們在積極地招募美國民眾
We believe they are actively recruiting American citizens.
因此  政府要申請
Accordingly, the government is requesting
在主干網上攔截電話和網絡流量
702章上游監控令
a Section 702 upstream surveillance order.
-國內監控  -監控流量  不是個人
- Domestic surveillance. - Monitoring traffic, not individuals.
上前
Approach the bench.
外國情報監視法法庭  機密判決的閉門的
The FISA Court. Classified rulings behind closed doors.
就連他們都不知道我們今早派去了律師
Not even these men know we have a lawyer in there this morning.
哈里發國已經控制了三個油田
ICO already has three oil fields under their control.
俄羅斯減產時
They made a fortune selling crude
他們靠賣原油大掙了一筆
when Russia cut down production.
這是間接后果  先生  我們有責任做出回應
It's blowback, sir. It's our responsibility to address it.
如果我們發動襲擊  只會讓更多極端分子瘋狂
If we launch strikes, we radicalize even more extremists.
先生  他們的軍隊會壯大的
Sir, their army will grow.
艾哈邁迪兄弟是前復興社會黨黨員
The Ahmadis are former Baathists
有很硬的生意關系
with strong business ties.
如果現在出擊  可以趁他們還沒壯大砍下它的頭
We can cut the head off before they get bigger if we strike now.
如果威脅等級提升  我們再重新考慮
If the threat level increases, we'll reassess.
先生  我們時機有限
Sir, we have a very limited window.
將軍  總統已經決定了
General, the president's made his decision.
非常感謝  二位先生
Thank you very much, gentlemen.
我是批過一些比較過分的申請  史蒂夫
I have rubber-stamped some borderline requests, Steve,
-但這也  -我知道
- but this is very-- - I know.
我也覺得驚訝
I was surprised, too.
但這是直接來自白宮的意思
But it's straight from the White House.
這得要點時間了
Well, this is going to take some time.
我得好好審核一下
I have to do a proper review.
這把槍是一個職業罪犯非法地
This gun was illegally obtained by a career criminal
在一個不強制背景審查的槍展上購得的
at a gun show where background checks aren't mandatory.
這把槍在一次常規交通違章處理中
This gun killed Officer Dempsey's partner
打死了鄧普西警官的搭檔
at a routine traffic stop.
這把是在網上購得  完全沒有背景審查
This one was ordered on the Internet. No background checks.
這把槍打死了鮑勃和蘇·格蘭特14歲的兒子
This gun killed Bob and Sue Grant's 14-year-old son.
這是打死了艾德華·密查姆特工的那把槍
And this is the gun that killed Agent Edward Meechum.
艾德華·H·密查姆
沒幾個特勤局特工能葬在阿林頓國家公墓
Not many Secret Service agents buried at Arlington.
我認為這是他應得的
I'd say he earned his place.
我沒有意識到  他對我是多么重要
I took it for granted, how important he was to me,
我多么依賴他
how much I leaned on him.
現在他死了  我才看明白
It's clear to me now, now that he's gone.
我不想對你犯同樣的錯誤  唐納德
I don't wanna make the same mistake with you, Donald.
什么意思
How do you mean?
我之前沒意識到我多么倚重你
I didn't realize how much I lean on you.
我中槍之后  你應對一切的手腕
The way you handled everything after I was shot,
堪稱大師
it was masterful.
我...也就是勉強維持吧
Well, I... I guess I kept my head above water.
克萊爾跟我說了你給予了多大的支持
Claire told me how supportive you were,
證明了自己是怎樣一位天生的領導者
what a natural leader you proved to be.
我想要這樣的人留在身邊  唐納德
I want that by my side, Donald,
就像密查姆生前那樣  我想要你做我的競選搭檔
the same way that Meechum was, as my running mate.
你要我做競選搭檔
You want me on the ticket?
據總統只有一步之遙  現在得嚴肅對待了
A heartbeat away from the presidency is a serious matter now.
康威是個不好對付的對手
Conway is a tough opponent.
我沒想到你會想要我
I never expected you'd want me.
我以為我只是個占座的
I thought I was just a placeholder.
不  我們能贏的  唐納德  你和我聯手
No, we can win, Donald. You and I, together.
這行嗎  弗蘭克
I don't know, Frank.
你需要一個對此十分渴求的人
You need someone who's hungry for this.
我不是很會競選
I'm not a great campaigner.
-佛蒙特州幫不上你  -你有很深的責任感
- Vermont doesn't help you. - You have a deep sense of duty,
就像這里埋葬的所有為國捐軀的男男女女
like all the men and women here who served their country,
這對我來說比策略重要多了
and that's far more important to me than strategy.
老實說  我不知道我是不是想要  弗蘭克
To be honest, I don't know if I want it, Frank.
我接手的時候  那份壓力  責任
When I had to take over, the stress, the responsibility...
兩周的總統已經是我的承受極限了
Two weeks as president was about as much as I can handle.
我好失望  唐納德
I'm disappointed, Donald.
但我理解
But I understand.
我不會逼迫你
And I won't pressure you.
我們開始吧
Should we do this?
好了
Okay.
如果不是我  你有其他人選嗎
Do you have other folks in mind, if it isn't me?
我們或許該聯系一下領導層
Well, we should probably reach out to the leadership,
詢問他們的意見
and get their advice.
但你是對的
But you're right.
不管是誰  得是一個對此十分渴求的人
Whoever it is, they need to be hungry for it.
這些死亡本都可以避免
All of these deaths could have been prevented.
因此
And that's why
我在跟一個參議員聯盟合作  出臺一部法律
I'm working with a coalition of senators to introduce a law
對所有槍支交易都進行背景審查
that will extend background checks to all gun transactions,
包括槍支展和在線銷售
including gun shows and online sales.
我想說清楚  這不是針對槍支持有的打擊
And let me be clear, this is not an assault on gun ownership.
而是對非法持有槍支的打擊
It's an assault on illegal gun ownership.
我現在將回答問題
I'll now take questions.
有請下任美國總統
The next President of the United States,
我的摯愛  一個母親最好的伴侶
the love of my life, the best father a mother could hope for,
我丈夫  威爾·康威
my husband, Will Conway.
康威  康威  康威
Conway! Conway! Conway!
紐約  你們好
Hello, New York!
他在所有戰場州都以兩位數領先
He's ahead by double digits in every battleground state.
共和黨全國委員會籌集了我們兩倍的錢
The RNC is raising two-to-one what we have.
-這人是個搖滾明星  -我們需要自己的搖滾明星
- This guy is a rock star. - We need our own rock star.
您在考慮誰  總統先生
Who are you thinking of, Mr. President?
唐納德·布萊斯
Donald Blythe.
您不覺得有策略上更好的選擇嗎
Uh, don't you think there's a more strategic choice?
這就是出于策略考慮
I am being strategic.
鄧巴退出是一碼事
Look, it's one thing that Dunbar's dropped out,
但我們得拉攏她的支持者
but we have to get her supporters.
唐納德·布萊斯一身清廉
And Donald Blythe, he oozes integrity.
他可以幫我們把那些
He can help us get all of those
幻想破滅的選民拉回我們的陣營
disillusioned people back into our camp.
大選中的溫和派呢
What about moderates in the general?
我們需要一個來自搖擺州的人
We need somebody from a swing state.
而且有殷實的籌款途徑
With deep fundraising pockets.
我們可以拿唐納德的經驗做賣點
Well, look, we can sell Donald's experience.
他已經替過班
He's filled the shoes.
為什么要半途換馬啊
I see no reason to change horses midstream.
他的資質不夠多
He doesn't check off enough columns.
我們需要個斗士  而不是個教授
We want a fighter, not a professor.
我同意  先生  我們能找到比布萊斯更好的
I agree, sir. We can do better than Blythe.
我實在想不出還有誰比
Well, I am hard-pressed to come up with anyone better
真正坐在過那張桌子后面的人更有資格
than a man who actually knows what it's like to sit at that desk.
我們可以給您提幾個名字
We can offer you some names.
-他會很難過的  -我去跟他談
- He'll be devastated. - Let me talk to him.
不  還是我來  我去找他談吧
No, it's better that I do. Let me talk to him.
我們馬上給您準備名單
We'll get you that list right away.
好吧  如果你能想到其他人選
Well, all right. If you can come up with some alternatives,
我絕對愿意聽聽  多謝各位
I'm certainly willing to listen. Thank you all very much.
我認為最好的政府  是職權最有限的
And I believe the best government is that which governs least.
這并非新的思想  而是個老的
That's not a new idea. It's an old one.
是我黨創始人  杰弗遜說的
The founder of our party, Jefferson, said it.
我們得賦予它新生
We need to make it new again.
我們需要一個不干擾人民生活的政府
We need a government that doesn't interfere with people's lives,
不打擾他們的自由  他們對幸福的追求
with their liberty, with their pursuit of happiness.
這不正是我們需要保護的嗎
Isn't that what we need to protect?
是的
Yes.
而這正是安德伍德總統最讓我們失望之處
And that's where President Underwood is failing us the most.
道格  那個進展...
Doug, where are we on the, uh--
外國情報監視法法庭還得要一陣  法官不太情愿
FISA Court could take a while. The judge was reluctant.
我還是應該安排一次會面
I should set up a meeting anyway.
我一直不喜歡這個計劃  先生
I've never liked this plan, sir.
我覺得拿到法庭裁決之前我們不該妄動
I don't think we should do anything until we get the court ruling.
A計劃已經啟動了  我們先看看結果吧
Plan A is in motion, let's let that pan out first.
如果A計劃成功  那么波利跳就不是問題了
If plan A works, then fine, Pollyhop is no longer a problem,
但如果不成功  我得開始打基礎了
but if it doesn't, I need to start laying the groundwork.
-麥卡倫沒那么好說服  -我們不了解此人
- Macallan could take some convincing. - We don't know this man--
我們現在并不非得擴大圈子
Yeah, we don't absolutely need to widen the circle right now.
是非得  先生
We do, sir.
光是啟動這樣的監控行動就得要好幾周
Just to get this sort of surveillance operational can take weeks.
但道格說得對
Yeah, but Doug is right.
我們不了解他  他對我們是個陌生人
We don't know him. He's a stranger to us.
他是國內  或許是全世界最棒的數據科學家
He is the top data scientist in the country, maybe the world.
-他曾研究行為浸染...  -行了
- He was exploring behavior adoption and immersing... - Stop.
這可是國內監控  莉安
We are talking domestic surveillance, LeAnn.
我唯一在乎的理論就是風險和票數的比例
And the only theory I'm interested in is risk versus votes.
他能幫我們拉到票
And he gets us the votes.
您沒聽到領導層的話嗎
Didn't you hear the leadership?
他們說康威要把我們滅掉了
They said Conway is destroying us.
麥卡倫能逆轉這一點  他能幫我們拿下選舉
Macallan reverses that, he wins us the election.
"哈里發國占領了庫爾德要塞"
"ICO occupies Kurdish stronghold."
有多少人聽說過哈里發國
How many of you have heard of ICO?
他們是穆斯林極端分子  在敘利亞攻占油田
They're Muslim extremists taking over oil fields in Syria.
媒體對他們幾乎鮮有報道
The media is barely covering them
就因為白宮對此睜一只眼閉一只眼
because the White House is turning a blind eye.
作為紐約州長
As the Governor of New York...
我無法對恐怖主義視而不見
I can't turn a blind eye to terrorism
因為它曾發生在我們家門口
because it's been right here on our doorstep.
知道911發生時我做了什么嗎
You know what I did when 9/11 happened?
我加入了空軍  因為我想為國盡忠
I joined the Air Force because I wanted to serve my country,
就像我祖父那樣
just like my grandfather did
他當年就在這個碼頭登上了一艘運輸艦
when he boarded a transport ship on this very dock
前往太平洋  與日本人作戰
and sailed to the Pacific to fight the Japanese.
等我的孩子長大了
When my children grow up...
查理和莉莉
Charlie and Lily...
我希望我能看著他們的眼睛
I wanna be able to... to look them in the eye...
告訴他們  我曾為你們而戰
and tell them that I fought for you.
我曾為你們的未來而戰
I fought for your future.
在我看來  那個未來很明確
And to me, that future is clear.
就是小政府  減稅收
Less government, less taxes,
更加自由  保護自由
more freedom, protect that freedom!
非常感謝  謝謝  謝謝
Thank you so much. Thank you, thank you.
州長  能否說說您和搜索引擎
Governor, can you comment on your relationship
波利跳的關系
with the search engine Pollyhop?
波利跳是否真的在向您提供選民數據
Is it true Pollyhop is providing you with voter data?
-馬上把格蘭特叫來  -他好像在加州
- I want Grant here, right away. - Uh, he's in California I think.
他有兩架私人飛機  選一架飛過來
He's got two Gulf Streams. Have him pick one.
非常感謝  謝謝你  保重
Thank you so much, thank you. Thank you, take care.
波利跳是否真的在向您提供選民數據
Is it true Pollyhop is providing you with voter data?
-提問被人拍下了  -他回應了嗎
- The question was caught on camera. - Did he answer it?
沒有  網上已經有很多關注了
No. It's getting a lot of traction online.
到早上應該報道滿天飛了
Should be all over the news by morning.
讓賽斯把目前為止的報道和簡報都拿給我
Have Seth send me all the stories and clips so far.
我覺得我現在不需要去見莉安的人
I don't think I have to meet LeAnn's guy now.
-A計劃會好使的  -不不
- Plan A's gonna work. - No, no, no.
去見他  這并不能定下來什么
Meet with him. Look, it doesn't commit us to anything.
-先生  -聽著  我跟你一樣也不想走這條路
- Sir- - Look, I don't wanna go down this route any more than you do,
但至少也算面面俱到了
but at least we'll have our bases covered.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
想象一個決斗在我和康威之間展開
Imagine a duel. Me and Conway.
康威有一把厲害的槍  一個搜索引擎
Now, Conway has a powerful gun, a search engine.
之所以厲害  是因為靠它
And it's powerful because with it,
他就能知道你在想什么  你想要什么
he can tell what you think, what you want,
你在哪  你是誰
where you are and who you are.
他可以把這些搜索都變成票
He can turn all those searches into votes,
這些子彈足夠打死我的勝算
and that's enough bullets to kill my chances of winning.
但我有把更大的槍  叫做國家安全局
But I have an even bigger gun. It's called the NSA.
這就是做總統的優勢之一
It's one of the perks of being president.
如果法庭批準我進行監控的話
That is, if the courts allow my surveillance request.
我猜掛在這墻上的男人
I imagine the men hanging on these walls
也希望他們當時有那樣的一把槍
wished they'd had a gun like that available to them.
你的手機  你身旁那個人的手機
Your phone, the phone of the person sitting next to you,
你鄰居的手機  你認識的每個人
your neighbor's phone and everyone you know
和你不認識的三億美國人
and the 300 million Americans you don't know.
我能看到你  我能用我所見  操縱這次選舉
I can see you, and I can use what I see to rig this election.
當然  這樣的武器
Now, of course, a weapon like that,
可以想見  風險有多大
well, you can imagine how risky it is.
可能他那樣的老壞蛋都會覺得猶豫呢
Huh, it might have even given pause to an old crook like him.
就因為監聽了水門大廈的
I mean, they roasted him on the spit
幾個房間  他就被人吊打
for tapping into a few rooms at the Watergate.
我可是要監聽每一個美國家庭
I'm talking about tapping into every single home in America.
這樣的武器  有可能在我手中爆炸
And a weapon like that could blow up in my hand
所以這是B計劃  A計劃要安全得多
and that's why it's plan B. Plan A is much safer.
曝光康威在違法使用他的槍
Expose that Conway is using his gun illegally
將他的武器從他手中奪下
and remove the weapon from his hand.
我們三個都挨過子彈
All three of us took bullets.
我知道我們為什么要笑  我們活下來了
Well, I know why we're smiling. We survived.
艾丹  這位是道格·斯坦普
Aidan. This is Doug Stamper.
嗯  我知道他是誰
Yeah, I know who he is.
為什么找我來
Tell me why I'm here.
國內監控  我們要贏下一場選舉
Domestic surveillance. We need to win an election.
-你認真的嗎  -如果是呢
- You serious? - What if we were?
國安局
The NSA...
-你愿冒這樣的險  -如果你值得信任
- You'd take that risk? - If you can be trusted.
你的每一條理論
Every theory you have ever had,
你想檢驗的一切
everything you have ever wanted to test.
作為回報  你得到什么
And in return, you get what?
選民數據  好知道該針對誰
Voter data? So you know who to target?
以及如何找到他們  影響他們
And how to target them, to influence them.
給他們洗腦嗎
To brainwash them?
這是為了康威  波利跳的事
Oh, this is about Conway, the Pollyhop thing.
-我就不該告訴你的  -我們是在浪費時間嗎
- I never should've told you that. - Are we wasting our time?
我不能安排任何人去做
I couldn't put a single person on this.
-不  這太危險  -談話結束
- No. It's radioactive. - We're done.
-到此為止  -要怎么做啊
- This is over. - How would this even work?
獲得主干網權限...
To get backbone access requires--
我們在爭取一個外國情報監視法判決  反恐
We're getting a FISA ruling, counter-terrorism.
我從未在國安局中過標
I've never won a bid from the NSA--
-莉安  我們走吧  -你能贏
- LeAnn, let's go. - You'd win the bid.
這就是你想要的  艾丹
This is what you want, Aidan.
老天
Jesus.
你來是想看能不能信任我
You came here to see if you can trust me.
我怎么知道我能信任你
How do I know I can trust you?
我不在乎你是不是信任我
I don't care whether you trust me or not.
但如果我們走上這條路
But if we go down this road,
萬一出事  你得背鍋
you take the fall if anything goes wrong.
不是我們  不是總統  是你
Not us, not the president. You.
只能這樣
It's the only way this works.
告訴我你覺得是不是值得
So you tell me if you think it's worth it.
價值
The worth.
你根本不了解
You have no idea.
多謝你能來
Thank you so much for coming.
-杰弗里  -州長
- Jeffrey! - Governor.
你怎么樣  多謝你
How you doing? Thank you so much.
賣下了一整張桌子  你對我們太好了
Buying a whole table. I mean, you've just been so great to us.
為你什么都行  州長  能合個影嗎
Anything for you, Governor. Can I get a photo?
當然
Of course.
你怎么樣  里奇
How you doing, Rich?
波利跳的事是真的嗎
Is this, uh, Pollyhop thing true?
漢娜也一起拍吧  漢娜
Let's get Hannah in this. Hannah.
-杰弗  -漢娜  見到你真高興
- Oh, Jeff. - Hannah, good to see you.
-我也是  你怎么樣  -格蘭特先生來了
- Good to see you. How are you? - Mr. Grant is here.
我很好  你呢
I'm good, how are you?
杰弗里  我回頭再找你  我就回來
Jeffrey, I'm gonna come find you, okay? I'll be right back.
-好  -我們拍吧
- Okay. - Let's do it.
我接到了《紐約時報》的電話
I'm getting calls from The New York Times.
這事現在是瞞不住了
There is no way we can keep a lid on this now.
我們接到了來自各方的電話
We're getting calls from everyone.
如果媒體真的深挖
If the media really digs their feet in,
別考慮公眾的反應了
forget about the public response.
我們得擔心司法部了
We need to worry about the Justice Department.
你說我們的做法并不違法
You said what we're doing wasn't illegal.
不  我說是灰色地帶  不受監管
No, I said it was gray, that it's unregulated.
我們的數據是私有的
Our data is proprietary.
我們如何使用  是我們的特權
How we want to use it, it's our prerogative.
如果他們給分享那些數據的利益估價
If they put a value on the benefits of sharing all that data,
肯定要超過所有競選經費上限
the figure would break all campaign finance caps there are.
這事怎么泄露出去的
How the fuck did this get out?
先生  那名記者不是我們記者團的
Sir? That reporter's not in our press pool.
-我們沒給他認證  -那么他為誰工作
- We didn't credential him ourselves. - So, who does he work for?
我們還在努力查證
We're still trying to track that down.
把你的手機給我
Give me your phone.
我這就給您接通  先生
I'll connect you now, sir.
您在跟總統通話了
You are now on with the president.
我得說  我很失望
I must say, I'm disappointed.
我還希望我們第一次見面會是當面見呢
I was hoping the first time we met would be in person.
-我們見過的  -是啊  對了
- We've met before. - Oh, yes, that's right.
你知道我打來是為什么事  總統先生
You know why I'm calling, Mr. President.
不知道  但我的確讀到了一些有趣的文章
No, but I have been reading some curious articles.
你覺得這些報道要多久就會成為主流
How long before you think it becomes mainstream?
你安排了那名記者
You planted that reporter.
我可沒有  你是謬贊我了
I did not. You're giving me far more credit than I deserve.
如果你把司法部扯進來
If you bring the Justice Department into this,
我會在濫用職權上對你窮追猛打
I'll come down hard on you for abuse of power,
那對你的傷害不會少于對我的傷害
and that'll hurt you just as much as it hurts me.
我不用  他們跟其他人一樣
I won't have to. They read the newspapers,
也會看報紙
just like everyone else.
那你最好拉住他們
Well, then you better hold them back.
我提醒你一下  州長
Let me remind you, Governor,
以防你哪天真當上了總統
in case you do become president one day,
司法部是自主的
the Justice Department is autonomous.
我干涉可是違法的
If I were to intervene, it would be illegal.
就像你搶了聯邦應急管理署那次嗎
Just like when you raided FEMA?
瞧  全國都想相信你腐敗
See, the country wants to believe that you're corrupt,
我會畫道線把你和...
and I'll draw a very clear line between you--
你做吧  這事鬧得越大越好
Go ahead. The more volume on this, the better.
你提出指控  我就讓媒體以事實回應
You hurl accusations, I'll let the press hurl facts.
但你究竟想做什么呢
But what did you really hope to achieve?
我覺得你浪費了時間
I think you've wasted your time.
你真有籌碼的時候該打給我的
You should have called me when you had some actual leverage.
但我得說  聽到你如此激動真是令人喜出望外
But I must say, it is a treat to hear you so worked up.
多謝了
I do thank you for that.
"華盛頓  杰弗遜  林肯
"Washington, Jefferson, Lincoln.
高個子能當好總統"  我們初遇時你對我說的
Tall men make good presidents." You said that when we first met.
是的  我記得
Yes, I remember what I said.
你當時怕了
You were intimidated.
我并不低估你  州長  但怕你
I don't underestimate you, Governor. But intimidated?
光是海拔和自大可不足以讓我害怕
Takes a lot more than height and arrogance to intimidate me.
你趕快回你的律師身邊吧
You better get back to all your lawyers.
羅馬將軍蘇拉
When the Roman general Sulla,
大約我現在這年紀時
who was about the same age I am now,
向羅馬進軍  清除城內叛軍
marched on Rome to purge the city of usurpers,
當時血流成河
it was a bloodbath.
他最大的對手是一個叫馬呂斯的年輕人
His greatest rival was a young man named Marius,
才26歲
who was just 26 years old.
蘇拉殺了他之后
And after Sulla had him killed,
他在廣場上舉起了他的頭
he held up his head in the forum
盯著男孩無光的眼睛說
and looked into the boy's dead eyes
"首先  你得學會搖槳
and said, "First, you must learn to pull an oar.
然后才能掌舵"
Only then can you take the helm."
高壓110  低壓80  不賴嘛
110 over 80. Not bad.
威爾
Will.
我打給了總統
I called the president.
是個錯誤
It was a mistake.
好吧
Okay.
聽著  我們回樓上去
Look, um... why don't we go back upstairs
籌點錢吧
and collect some money?
好嗎  大家都想見你
Okay? Everyone wants to see you.
-走吧  -你會想出對策的
- Let's go. - You'll figure it out.
康威打來了  想跟我做交易
Conway called. He wanted to make a deal.
肯定很有意思吧
I'm sure that was enjoyable.
等司法部插手了
It will be even more so
會更有意思的
once the Justice Department gets involved.
那是...
Is that the, uh...
同款  不是同一個
Same model. Not the actual one.
-特勤局居然允許...  -那個
- Surprised the Secret Service let - Well,
他們拔了撞針
they removed the firing pin.
比我想的要輕
It's lighter than I imagined.
這么小的東西居然能造成那么大的傷害
It's amazing something this small could do that much damage.
我本想明天帶上的
I was gonna bring it tomorrow,
但或許太戲劇化了
but I think it might be too theatrical.
要我幫你練習嗎
You want me to help you practice?
好
All right.
早上好  安德伍德夫人
Good morning, Mrs. Underwood.
早上好  梅爾曼女士
Good morning, Ms. Melman.
-不  她叫什么  -茱莉亞
- No, what's her first name? - Julia.
-叫這個  -我們不認識
- Use that. - We've never met before.
讓她知道第一夫人是誰
Remind her who the First Lady is.
早上好  茱莉亞
Good morning, Julia.
早上好  安德伍德夫人
Good morning, Mrs. Underwood.
請坐吧
Please, have a seat.
我們想有包容性
We want to be inclusive.
我們希望全國步槍協會與我們合作讓法案通過
We'd like the NRA to work with us on getting this bill passed.
我們在兩黨都廣受支持
We have major support on both sides of the aisle.
那是現在  但今后未必
Well, you do for now, but not for long.
即便是20個孩子死于校園槍擊
You can have 20 kids massacred in a school shooting.
公眾會憤怒呼吁槍支改革
There's always the usual public outcry, demands for gun reform.
但幾個月后  人們就會忘記
But a few months go by and people forget.
這份法案會迅速通過國會
Well, this will move through Congress quickly.
我們在兩黨都廣受支持
We've got major support on both sides of the aisle.
那也不足以抵抗阻撓議事
Not enough to break a filibuster.
我們會把此事拖到大選
We'll drag this out till the election.
我們會阻撓參議院其他所有的法案
We'll tie up every other bill in the Senate.
我跟很多參議員談過  他們...
Well, I've spoken to a lot of Senators and they--
不  別跟她糾纏那個
No, don't get bogged down there.
把重點直接戳到最高法院
Pivot right to the Supreme Court.
你打算連最高法院提名也拖延嗎
You plan on holding up the Supreme Court nomination, as well?
除非你打算提名一位全國步槍協會的成員
Unless you're going to nominate an NRA member.
-你知道那不可能  -雅各布斯不好預測
- You know we can't do that. - Jacobs was unpredictable.
這次我們不會冒險了
This time we're not taking any chances.
如果你讓政府停擺
If you bring the government to a standstill,
我們就把全國步槍協會作為選舉重點
we're gonna make this election about the NRA.
你拼不過一個億的廣告
You can't match $100 million in ad buys.
去吧  把你的錢都浪費掉吧
Go for it. Flush your money down the drain.
民主黨數十年前就輸了這場仗了
The Democrats lost that battle decades ago.
你還會再輸一次
And you'll lose it again.
總統任黨鞭時未提出過一項槍支改革法案
The president never offered up one gun reform bill while he was whip.
因為那當時并非他的首要考慮
Well, because it wasn't a top priority for him--
不不不  更強勢點
No, no, no, no, no. Make it, uh, stronger.
比如  "總統挨了顆子彈"  弄成私事
Say, uh, "The president took a bullet!" Make it personal.
我對您丈夫遭槍擊感到遺憾
I'm sorry your husband got shot.
但不至于因此妥協
But not enough to roll over.
我們不是叫你妥協
Oh, we're not asking you to.
我們是希望你站在歷史正確的一方
We're inviting you to be on the right side of history.
這不錯  但你得拿出致命的招數
Yeah, that's good, but you wanna go in for the kill.
我們要這女人氣得奪門而出
We want this woman storming out of that door,
口吐白沫
foaming at the mouth.
好吧  別丟人了  茱莉亞
All right. Don't disgrace yourself, Julia.
-想想未來  -不  再強硬點
- Think about the future- - No, tougher.
再狠點  再強硬點
Stronger, tougher!
好吧  那這樣如何
All right, what about...
三十年后  當你接受臨終護理  奄奄一息時
Thirty years from now when you're dying in hospice care...
你可以回首人生  為你拯救的生命而自豪
you can look back and be proud of all the lives you saved.
也可以被歷史遺忘
Or you can be forgotten...
用你冰冷僵硬的雙手緊緊抓住過去
clutching onto the past with your cold, dead hands.
我自己出去吧
I'll show myself out.
這就是我說的那份勇氣
That's exactly the steel goddamn stomach I was talking about.
是皮特·德雷爾嗎
Was it Pete Dreyer?
德雷爾議員是我多年的導師
Congressman Dreyer's been a mentor for years.
-他無權告訴你  -他完全有權
- He had no right to tell you. - He had every right.
如果眾議院情報委員會的成員
If a member of the House Intelligence Committee
決定對我透露情報  他有這個權利
chooses to share information with me, he's at liberty to do so.
我們的談話是私下的
Our conversation was in confidence.
這讓我很不舒服
I don't feel comfortable with this.
議員跟你一樣覺得不滿
The Congressman is just as frustrated as you are,
他找到我是因為想幫忙
and he spoke to me because he wants to help.
我也想幫忙  將軍
And so do I, General.
州長  我是名士兵  我不玩政治
Governor, I'm a soldier. I'm not going to play politics.
你對皮特開口的時候就是在玩政治了
You played politics the moment you opened your mouth to Pete.
-你看到我昨天的講話了嗎  -是的
- Did you see my speech yesterday? - Yes, I did.
我都是真心的
I meant every word of it.
你我都曾為我們國家而戰
Now, you and I have both fought for our country.
安德伍德可沒有
Underwood hasn't.
他根本不懂  不能理解
He has no idea. He doesn't understand.
所以我得當上總統
And that's why I need to be president,
這樣我們才能在需要的時候出擊
so we can strike when we need to strike.
聽著  我可以幫你  但我需要你的幫助
Look, I can help you, but I need your help to do so.
我從未向媒體透露過機密信息  從沒有過
I've never leaked classified information to the press. Not once.
我的同事干過  我沒有過
My colleagues have. I haven't.
有個更好的辦法
There's a better way.
你起初會覺得不太好
You're not gonna like the sound of this at first,
但聽我說完  我們是可以回擊的
but if you hear me out, we can fight back on this.
-將軍  -總統先生
- General. - Mr. President.
收回去吧  我不接受你的辭職
You can take this back. I am not accepting your resignation.
請坐
Please, sit.
我曾在黎巴嫩作戰  先生
I fought in Lebanon, sir.
在索馬里  波斯尼亞
Commanded troops in Somalia,
兩次海灣戰爭和阿富汗帶過兵
in Bosnia, in both Gulf Wars, in Afghanistan.
我不希望我們再在那樣的沖突中陷入困境
I just don't wanna see us bogged down in another conflict like those.
哈里發國就是下一個基地組織和塔利班
ICO is the next Al Qaeda and Taliban.
而你辭職不會有任何用
And you accomplish nothing by resigning your commission.
您現在的政策才是毫無用處
We've accomplished nothing with your current policy.
我不禁覺得
You know, I just can't help but think that...
這時機  太巧了
the timing of this, it's just a bit coincidental.
-什么  -康威昨天發表了一番高談闊論
- Sir? - Well, Conway gave a big speech yesterday.
他把哈里發國吹得很大  是吧
I mean, he made a big meal out of ICO, didn't he?
他應該是意識到了他們多么危險
I suppose he realizes just how dangerous they are.
不知這情報他是從哪得來的
I wonder where he's getting that information.
我不知道  先生
I've no idea, sir.
我從未跟他說過話  我也不會那么做
I've never spoken to the man, nor would I.
那是機密
It's classified.
那么你的話是發自良心
And you're speaking from your conscience.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
良心有種標志性的臭味兒
Conscience has an unmistakable stink to it,
就像生洋蔥和早上的口臭
sort of like raw onions and morning breath.
但謊言的臭味兒
But a lie stinks even more
從一個不習慣撒謊的人身上散發出來  格外濃烈
when it's coming from someone who isn't used to lying.
就像臭雞蛋和馬糞
It's more like rotten eggs and horseshit.
-我們多快能采取行動  -您想采取行動嗎
- How soon can we move on this? - You want to conduct the mission?
這能避免你辭職嗎
Would it keep you from resigning?
我...
Well, I--
我需要你的專業知識和經驗
I need your expertise and your experience,
如果兩者都告訴我我錯了
and if both are telling me I'm wrong,
那么比起我自己  我更相信你的直覺
I'd rather trust your instincts than mine.
現在還有機會嗎
Do we still have an open window?
集會將于明晚結束
The gathering is set to end by tomorrow night.
我先去跟參聯會主席和國防部長談談
Let me talk to the Chairman and the Secretary of Defense
-然后再簽署命令  -當然  先生
- before I sign off on the order. - Of course, sir.
將軍  跟總統針鋒相對  真是勇敢
General, it takes a brave man to stand up to a president.
如果您批準行動  我們就拿不到裁決了
If you authorize the mission, we won't get our court ruling.
哈里發國如果被消滅
There is no way to justify
就不能作為國內監控的理由了
domestic surveillance once ICO is eliminated.
這沒關系  媒體壓力越來越大
Which is fine, because media pressure is mounting.
康威別無選擇  只能跟波利跳撇清關系
Conway has no choice but to distance himself from Pollyhop.
我們不知道結局會如何
We don't know how that's gonna play out.
我可以告訴你們布洛哈特的辭職結局會如何
Oh, I can tell you how Brockhart's resignation is gonna play out.
每個搖擺州30秒的廣告
Thirty-second ads in every swing state.
一位功勛卓著的老兵
A decorated war veteran
痛擊我們不重視國家安全
pulverizing us for being weak on national security.
波利跳對我們的打擊會遠勝于布洛哈特
Pollyhop is gonna pulverize us more than Brockhart ever could.
如果康威要忙著應付公眾批評就不會了
Not if Conway is busy fighting public outcry.
想想他們已經收集到的數據
Think about the data they have already gathered.
你向我們提出時  說這是沒辦法的辦法
When you sold us this, you said it was going to be a last resort,
而非唯一的辦法
not the only resort.
獲得監控批準毫無風險
There is no risk in getting surveillance approved.
然后我們要么用  要么不用
Then we either use it or we don't.
但如果您下令打擊  先生  我們就沒選擇了
But if you order this strike, sir, we don't even have the option.
-你見過麥卡倫了  -是  先生
- You've met with him, Macallan. - Yes, sir.
-他值得信任嗎  -我真說不準
- So, can he be trusted? - I honestly can't say.
他比您更明白其中的風險
He understands the risks even better than you do.
-我要下令打擊  -先生
- I'm gonna authorize the strike. - Sir...
你的人是無名小卒
Your guy's an unknown.
-布洛哈特可不是  -夫人
- Brockhart isn't. - Ma'am...
-我支持弗蘭西斯  -給我接國防部長
- I agree with Francis. - Get me the Secretary of Defense.
我叫克萊爾今天一起來
I've asked Claire to join us today
因為這直接與她
because this directly affects
想要通過的法律相關
the legislation she's trying to get passed.
你們競選搭檔的三個首選
Your top three choices for running mate,
都是反對槍支管制說客的朋友
they're all tight with the gun lobby.
安德伍德夫人
Mrs. Underwood...
你知道這屋里的人都贊同你想要的改革
You know everyone in this room agrees with the reforms you want,
但我們要考慮大選
but we're thinking about the general election,
而跟全國步槍協會交惡可很不明智
and the NRA is a terrible enemy for us to make.
惠特克會關注搖擺州  籌款
Yeah, now Whittaker's gonna focus on swing states, fundraising...
這時我就唱白臉
That's where I'll play the bad cop.
而你唱臉更白的  等我們打亂了他們的陣腳
You play the worse cop. Then when we get them off balance...
你就再重新唱起紅臉
You come back in again as the good cop.
沒錯  所以我就先說
Exactly. So I will start with...
我覺得這些選擇發出的訊息很混亂
Well, I feel that these choices send mixed messages.
我們支持槍支改革  他們不支持
We're for gun reform, they're not.
如果競選搭檔兩個人都是狂熱的槍支管制支持者
If both names on the ticket are gun-control fanatics,
那整個競選的重點就成了
then the whole election becomes about...
說私事  就像你讓我對付梅爾曼那樣
Get personal, the way you told me to with Melman.
四個總統里就有一個遭過槍擊
One out of four presidents gets shot at.
十個總統里有一個死于槍傷
One out of every ten dies from a bullet wound.
再強勢點
Better than that.
我看著艾德華·密查姆就死在我眼前
I saw Edward Meechum die before my very eyes.
-很好  你很幸運  -我很幸運
- Good. You were lucky. - I'm lucky.
數據對這些人來說毫無意義
Statistics don't mean anything to these people.
他們認為這條路只會通往沒收
They see this as a one-way road to confiscation.
如果我選擇這樣的立場會立刻失去席位
I lose my seat in a heartbeat if I take this stance.
-現在我要唱紅臉了  -好  博奇說
- Now, this is where I will play good cop. - Okay, so Birch goes,
"我們希望您能考慮全局  總統先生"
"We're asking you to look at the bigger picture here, Mr. President."
你說得對  鮑勃
You're right, Bob.
-克萊爾  -他們說得都對
- Claire! - They're all right. They are.
我跟全國步槍協會的見面并不順利
My meeting with the NRA did not go well.
他們打算全力以赴地阻撓此事
They're going to fight this tooth and nail.
當然了
Well, of course they are.
而且這項法案很可能不會通過
And... and the chances are the legislation won't pass.
會通過的  因為你們要讓法案
Oh, it'll pass. Because you are going to push it
通過參眾兩院  成為立法
until it goes through both houses and gets on the books.
我們現在雖然獲得支持
We may have support now...
但等法案進行表決的時候
But by the time this bill gets onto the floor...
你就專注于法案措辭吧  議員
You focus on the language, Congressman.
把說服美國人民交給我們
Leave convincing the American people to us.
如果你愿意在法案上與我們合作
Now, if you wanna work with us on this bill,
我就能容忍一個愛槍的候選人
I can stomach a gun-friendly candidate.
你呢  弗蘭西斯
What about you, Francis?
致命殺
The kill.
只有一個條件  克萊爾
Only on one condition, Claire.
我不希望我們為法案通過忙里忙外
I don't want us to work our asses off getting this bill passed
卻在法院被否決
just to see it knocked down in the courts.
這事我們無從控制  先生
We don't have any control over that, sir.
我們還得找人接替雅各布斯呢
We still need to fill Jacobs' seat.
如果你能找到反槍法官
If you can confirm an anti-gun justice,
我就讓愛槍人士做競選搭檔
I'll put a gun-lover on the ticket.
大選期間確認最高法院提名
A Supreme Court confirmation in the middle of an election?
拜托  有點膽子  鮑勃
Oh, come on, grow a pair, Bob.
我們都隨你的心了  也滿足我們一下嘛
We're giving you what you want. Give us what we want.
你在考慮誰
Who are you thinking about?
沒人跟你來吧
Nobody followed you?
沒人  我確定
No one. I'm positive.
有時候我會覺得我的學生不對勁
You know, sometimes I have a student and something seems off.
上大學有點太老了  知道嗎
They look a little too old, you know? To be in college.
-那是什么  -阿普唑侖[鎮靜劑]
- What is that? - Xanax.
盧卡斯來過
Lucas came up here.
來校園
To the campus.
他求我幫忙  我拒絕了
He wanted my help and I said no.
如果我答應了  或許他...
Maybe if I had, he wouldn't have...
太傻了
So stupid.
他出來了
He got out.
為什么要那么做
Why did he do this?
這就是我想查明的
That's what I'm trying to find out.
都是真的  湯姆
It's all true, Tom.
-你怎么知道  -我就是知道
- How do you know? - Because I know.
盧卡斯沒在遺書中提到你
Lucas didn't mention you in his suicide letter.
肯定是為了保護我
I'm sure it was to protect me.
如果你有任何證據  現在就該拿出來了
If you have any proof, now's the time to share it.
如果我有  你覺得還會發生這樣的事嗎
If I did, do you think any of this would've happened?
-你可以公開聲明  -我簽了宣誓書
- You could go on record- - I signed an affidavit.
我現在說什么都一文不值了
Anything I say now is worth shit.
或許就因為這個他們才沒再來找我
That's probably why they've left me alone.
不不  別再吃藥了
No, no. No. No more pills.
-答應我你會小心  -我保證
- Promise me you'll be careful. - I promise.
如果可以幫忙  我會的
I would help if I could, I--
你就好好照顧自己就行
You just focus on taking care of yourself.
過來  過來
Come here. Come here.
我能說服你改主意嗎
Is there anything I can do to make you reconsider?
是  先生  我理解
Yes, sir, I understand.
我也對發動打擊感到高興
I'm pleased the strike's on, as well.
多謝提醒  再見
Thank you for the heads up. Bye.
該死
Fuck!
-怎么了  -他屈服了
- What's wrong? - He caved.
-將軍嗎  -是的
- The general? - Yes.
爸爸  什么時候開始
Daddy, when is it?
什么時候開始  本
When is it? Ben?
我對這個沒把握  威爾  或許我們該取消
I'm not sure about this, Will. Maybe we should cancel it.
我的律師認為這主意糟透了
My lawyers are saying it's a terrible idea.
不是我們  就是司法部
If it's not us, it's the Justice Department.
-我為公司投入了一切  -相信我吧
- I've put everything into this company. - Just trust me on this.
威爾
Hey, Will.
-往我圖片分享上放  -嗯
- For my Insta. - Yeah.
笑一個查理
Okay. Smile, Charlie.
笑吧
Smile.
-好了  -真棒
- All right. - Great.
好了
Here we go.
你個小家伙
You little...
過去
Scoot over.
都好了嗎
Are we all set?
是的  先生  就等你了
Yes, sir. Ready whenever you are.
開始嘍
Here we go.
威爾·康威
正在進行網絡直播
好
Okay.
準備好了嗎  準備好了嗎
You ready? You ready?
嗯
Yep.
開始了
Here we go.
美國  你們好  我是威爾·康威
Hello, America. I'm Will Conway,
共和黨總統候選人
Republican candidate for president,
這是我兒子查理
and this is my son, Charlie.
跟大家打個招呼啊  查理
You wanna say hi to everyone, Charlie?
打個招呼  打個招呼吧
A little hi. Can we get a little hi?
不嗎  就這樣了  就這樣了
No? That's all we get? That's all we get.
這是我妻子漢娜  我們的小淘氣莉莉
And this is Hannah, my wife. And our little rascal Lily.
她已經不小了
Well, she's not so little anymore,
但絕對還是個小淘氣
but definitely still a rascal.
是吧  親愛的
Aren't you, sweetheart?
我們正在我們奧爾巴尼的家中進行網絡直播
And we are webcasting from our home here in Albany.
大家可以看到  我們不住在州長府
As you can see, we don't live in the governor's mansion.
我們跟你們很多人一樣  住在普通的民居中
We live in a regular house, just like many of you.
這是我們的起居室
And this is our living room.
一切都是漢娜自己裝修的
Hannah has decorated everything herself.
除了玩具
Well, except for the toys.
那是孩子們添加的裝飾
That's the... That's the kids' addition to the decor.
好多玩具
A lot of toys.
你們很多人都在新聞中看到或聽說了
Now, many of you have seen or read in the news
關于我們競選團隊跟搜索引擎波利跳合作的傳言
rumors about my campaign teaming up with the search engine Pollyhop,
我今天想跟大家談談這些傳言
and I'd like to speak to you today about those rumors
因為那根本不是傳言
because they're not rumors at all.
是事實  絕對真實
They're facts. One hundred percent accurate.
這位是我的好朋友本杰明·格蘭特
And here is my good friend Benjamin Grant.
他是波利跳的創始人
He's the founder of Pollyhop,
他會跟大家講講我們的合作
and he's gonna tell you about our partnership.
很多大公司都不參與政治
Well, a lot of big companies stay out of politics.
他們不想得罪人  但波利跳不是如此
They don't want to offend anyone. But not Pollyhop.
我們不遮掩我們的政治立場
We're not shy about who we support,
我們很驕傲能支持威爾·康威
and we're proud to support Will Conway.
他知道這個國家需要什么  將走向何方
He knows what this country needs and where it's going.
好了
Now...
我知道這可能會嚇到很多人
I realize this might scare a lot of people.
我們是否知道你的私人信息
Do we know your personal information?
我們是否能看到你們搜索了什么
Can we see what you're searching for?
我們是否在讀你們的郵件
Are we reading your emails?
答案是否定的  我們并未追蹤個人
The answer is no. We're not tracking individuals.
我們要的是元數據
We're looking at metadata,
宏觀瀏覽規律  搜索潮流  地域特征
large-scale browsing patterns, search trends, regional portraits.
因為本是對的
'Cause Ben is right.
一位總統應該了解他的選區
A president should know his constituents.
而網絡是了解的最佳工具
And the Internet is the best tool for that.
我見過數千人  跟很多人握過手
Now, I've met thousands of people and shaken a lot of hands,
但我不可能跟每個人見面
but I can't meet everyone.
這就是我傾聽數百萬人心聲的辦法
So this is my way of listening to millions of you.
如果我了解了你們
Now, it's only fair if I get to know you better,
那么你們也該了解我
you should get to know me better.
所以我雖然沒有讀你們的私人信件
So while I'm not reading your personal correspondence,
我希望你們能查看我的
I want you to have access to mine.
從今日起
So, from this point forward,
我通過這部手機發的郵件  短信
every email, text message, photo, or video
拍攝的照片和視頻
that I use on this phone,
你們都能看到  包括我當上州長后的一切
you can see it all, including everything since I became governor.
你們只需要登錄我的競選網站  網址是
Now, all you have to do is go into my campaign website at...
Conway2016.com
Conway2016.Com.
沒錯  你就能看到鏈接
That's correct. And you'll find a link right there.
我們的生活就是你的生活
Our life is your life.
你的未來是我們的未來
And your future is our future.
謝謝  天佑美國
Thank you, and God bless America.
-真不錯  -是啊  不錯
- That was good. - Yeah, that was good.
干得好  干得好
Well done. Well done.
不客氣  州長
You got it, Governor.
好了  我們拭目以待吧
All right. Now we wait and see.
康威直播大熱
他的誠實和坦誠造成了不小的影響
His honesty and openness have made quite an impact,
美國也豎起了耳朵
and America is paying attention.
康威網絡直播后三小時內
Just three hours since Conway's webcast,
就有超過兩百萬人登錄了他的網站
over two million people have visited his website...
波利跳流量激增
公眾的廣泛關注讓波利跳點擊量暴增
The massive public interest has driven traffic to Pollyhop.Com.
波利跳執行總裁本杰明·格蘭特
Pollyhop CEO Benjamin Grant
稱搜索量達到了平時的三倍
is reporting three times its normal volume of searches.
波利跳搜索趨勢
手機視頻全部上傳到了康威競選網站
All of the cell phone footage is on the Conway campaign website.
康威紅爆網絡
有超多的歷史影像
There's a ton of archived clips.
有些已經被瘋傳  包括這段
Some have already gone viral, including this one,
就拍攝于今天早上
filmed just this morning,
畫面中是康威和他美麗的妻子漢娜  好嫉妒啊
of Conway with his gorgeous wife Hannah, so jealous,
以及他萌爆的兒子查理
and his totally adorable son Charlie.
剃媽媽的頭  別剃我的
Shave Mom's head, not mine!
剃媽媽的頭
Shave Mom's head?
-好吧  -不
- Okay. - No!
猜對了  我還是討厭孩子
You guessed it. I still hate children.
大家根本不在乎自己的隱私
People don't care about their privacy.
他們希望他看
They want him to have access.
他依然違反了競選經費法規
He's still breaking campaign finance regulations.
但他得到的報道都是正面的
But he's getting good press,
而不是我們所期望的民憤
not the public outcry we had hoped for.
您不能讓司法部調查
You can't let the Justice Department investigate.
只會適得其反
It'll backfire on us.
您得取消空襲
What you need to do is call off the air strike.
先生  您已經簽署了命令
Sir, you've already signed the order.
飛機都升空了
We've got planes in the air.
我的工作是贏下競選  我得...
My job is to win a campaign, I need to have--
-我的工作是保護總統  -夠了
- And my job is to protect the president. - Enough!
老天爺
Jesus Christ.
走吧  我得跟他談談
Go. I need to speak with him.
你在想什么
What are you thinking?
當它只是B計劃時我還能接受
That I was fine with this when it was just plan B,
但這是國內監控
but this is... domestic surveillance.
我們都不認識這人
I mean, we don't even know this guy.
你說得對  我們不認識他  但我們知道
You're right, we don't know him. What we do know...
如果不采取措施  我們會輸
is we'll lose if we do nothing.
他們真美  是吧  康威夫婦
They're beautiful, aren't they? The Conways.
他們的青春  他們的兩個孩子
Their youth, their two little children.
這國家愛上了他們
The country is falling in love with them.
他們不會那樣愛我們的
They won't fall in love with us like that,
但我們有他們沒有的東西
but we have something they don't.
我們愿比任何人都走得更遠
We are willing to go one step farther than everyone else.
將軍  說句話
General, a word.
我們還有兩小時...
We're approximately two hours out--
-中止行動  -總統先生
- Abort the mission. - Mr. President?
-我命令你中止  -但您說
- I'm ordering you to abort. - But you said--
別逼我再說一遍了  也別威脅要辭職
Don't make me say it a third time, and don't threaten to resign,
因為我知道你不會的
because I know you won't,
因為你無法想象做個平民的滋味
because you can't even fathom what it means to be a civilian.
-執行我的命令  -是  先生
- Execute my order. - Yes, sir.
-先生  -已經下令了
- Sir. - It's done.
-先生  -我中止了
- Sir. - I aborted.
這么晚不睡
You're up late.
登錄康威的網站  2012年12月31日
Go to Conway's website. December 31st, 2012.
漢娜2012年的最后時刻
Hannah's last moments of 2012.
夠了  我在狼吞虎咽呢
Stop, I'm stuffing my face.
你在喂長身體的女孩嘛  小寶寶  你好啊
You're feeding a growing girl. Hello, little baby.
是啊
Yes, I am.
她在像個瘋子似的踢我
She's kicking like a maniac, too.
威爾  求你  別拍了
Will, please, stop.
-怎么了嘛  -別拍了
- No, come on. - No.
你有...你粘了點東西
You've got... You have... You have a little something...
當選州長先生
Mr. Governor-elect.
議員先生  見到您很榮幸
Congressman, such an honor to meet you.
-榮幸的是我  -這是我妻子  漢娜
- Well, the honor is mine. - This is my wife, Hannah.
榮幸  這是克萊爾
It's a pleasure. And this is Claire.
你好
Hello.
-幾個月了  -快七個月了
- How far along are you? - Almost seven months.
多謝您邀請我們來
Thank you so much for inviting us here.
這對我們太難得了
This is a real treat for us.
很高興你來了
Well, I'm glad you came.
我以為你今晚要去時代廣場呢
I thought you'd be in Times Square tonight.
德盧卡州長最后一年任職了
It's Governor De Luca's last year in office.
我覺得不該搶他的風頭
I thought he should have the spotlight to himself.
你太有風度了
Well, that's very classy of you.
而且我不想錯過
And I didn't wanna miss the chance to
在華盛頓結交新朋友的機會
make some new friends in Washington.
真是聰明  你見過加勒特了嗎
Well, that was a smart idea. Have you met Garrett, yet?
還沒呢  先生
No. No, sir.
來吧  女士們  我們就回來
Well, come on. Ladies, we'll be back.
當選總統先生  這是當選州長康威
Mr. President-elect, Governor-elect Conway.
-恭喜  -也恭喜您  先生
- Congratulations. - You, too, sir.
這就是他啊  那個金童  沒那么神秘嘛
So here he is, the boy wonder. He isn't a myth after all.
賤民差不多
More like a pariah.
-這里有好多民主黨人  -也有不少共和黨人
- There's a lot of Democrats here. - Plenty of Republicans, too.
這是弗蘭克張羅的
Frank made sure of that.
如果想在國會取得進展
Well, if you wanna push the sludge through Congress,
就得兩邊都有朋友
it's best to have grease on both sides of the aisle.
抱歉  我得走了  時間要到了
Oh, I'm sorry, I have to go. It's almost time.
-多謝你的服務  -謝謝您  先生
- Thank you for your service. - Thank you, sir.
你真是在911第二天就入伍了嗎
So, is it true that you joined up a day after 9/11,
還是只是一種說法
or is that just something you say?
24小時內  對天發誓
Within 24 hours, honest to God.
真是了不起
That's incredible.
我才25  剛從法學院出來
I was 25, just out of law school.
想步入仕途
You want a career in politics
偏巧趕上雙子塔的事
and the Twin Towers fall in your lap?
時機簡直再好不過
Timing couldn't have been better.
我明白你是怎么獲勝的了
Oh, I see how you won.
-他肯定像站在世界之巔  -我無法想象
- Well, he must be on top of the world. - I... I can't imagine.
是嗎  你多大  35
Oh, really? How old are you? Thirty-five?
36歲
Thirty-six.
你夜深人靜的時候從沒想過嗎
Oh, you've never thought about it, late at night?
-白宮嗎  -還能是什么
- The White House? - What else?
-你呢  -誰沒想過
- Have you? - Haven't we all?
我不急  誰知道呢  或許有一日吧
I'm in no rush. Who knows? Maybe, one day.
華盛頓  杰弗遜  林肯  高個子能當好總統
Washington, Jefferson, Lincoln. Tall men make great presidents.
你就好像希望我競選似的
It's like you want me to run.
天吶  可不  你競選
Oh, goodness, no. You running?
那對民主黨絕對是災難
That would be a disaster for the Democrats.
-我得去找我妻子了  -十
- I better see my wife. - Ten...
-我也是  -九
- Me, too. - ...nine,
八  七  六  五  四
eight, seven, six, five, four,
三  二  一
three, two, one!
新年快樂
Happy New Year!
-那還是一切開始之前  -是啊
- That was before everything. - I know.
弗蘭西斯  你在聽嗎
Francis, are you there?
我們要滅了他們
We're going to destroy them.
是的
Yes, we are.
■
2012年12月14日  康涅狄格州紐頓市發生特大槍擊案
20名六七歲的小學生被槍殺
事發后奧巴馬委任副總統拜登組織特別委員會
推動新槍支控制法案
但經過數月的運作  新法案仍全無機會通過國會
奧巴馬大發雷霆  但也束手無策
不久前  奧巴馬決定通過行政命令的方式
繞過國會  推動槍支管控
但這樣的努力即使成功  影響也非常有限
■
伊斯蘭國出現早期  美國政府和軍事機構就向白宮做過匯報
當時奧巴馬對這個恐怖組織非常輕視
認為他們是不入流的流寇  并輕蔑地諷刺說
一個中學校隊隊員穿上洛杉磯湖人隊的隊衣
也不會就變成科比·布萊恩特
目前包括曾經在奧巴馬政府任職的外交專家都認為
如果奧巴馬當初及時采取行動  伊斯蘭國不會發展到今天這樣
如此迅速地擴張成為歷史上最危險的恐怖組織
不僅在中東肆虐  也不放過在歐洲和美國發動大規模襲擊的機會